GORAN RADMANOVIC

1. Artiljerisjkog Puka 17, Gradiška 78400, BIH/RS • +387/065-899-867

goranradmanovic@gmail.com

linkedin.com/in/goran-radmanovic-70814a9b/

https://goranradmanovic.github.io/

Web Developer

Summary		
— Summary		

I'm a back-end & front-end web developer, who likes new technologies, challenges and new experience. I'm a quick learner and I work as a freelancer. You can easily find me and contact me through social accounts or on email address. It would be a great honor to work with you.

Hope to hear from you soon.

Work experience -

07.2019 - Present

Frontend Web Developer

OOMovers

I'm working remotely as a full stack web developer for company specialize in moving. My responsibility is to develop, maintain and upgrade company's website. Technology that I'm using are PHP & Silex framework, JS, HTML & CSS, SCSS, GIT ect.

03.2019 - 07.2019

Frontend Web Developer

Kompitenz

I worked as frontend web developer on frontend part of B2B web platform for one of the biggest Germany dairy industry. The web platform was connecting dairy manufacturer and the dairy industry as a buyer. Tech stack that I was using on that project was PHP (Laravel) and the VueJS as a frontend, and also SASS as CSS preprocessor.

11.2018 - 03.2019

Freelance Web Developer

Freelance (remote)

I worked on various web development project as full stack developer with technology stack mostly of PHP and JavaScript, project are different from classic web apps to moder PWA apps.

04.2016 - 11.2018 Web Developer

Alea Control

I worked on the frontend part of the betting and gambling apps for casinos and bookmaker. Also I was in contact with programmers from partner's company and with our clients from casinos and betting house. And one of my responsibility was to develop and maintain company's website. Main technology which I used was JS and AngularJS, HTML & CSS, GIT.

Lecture at the Course

09.2017 - 11.2017 Business Garden

07.2018 - 09.2018 I worked as a lecturer at the initial course of web development where I taught students

to the basics of HTML and CSS technology.

10.2015 - 03.2016 PHP Web Developer

BitLab

I worked on the web pages and web apps for clients. I also maintained legacy code. In addition, I worked in a team of developers and the main technologies that I used were PHP & Laravel framework, HTML & CSS, and also JavaScript.

11.2014 - 12.2014 Intern

OgoSense

I have successfully completed the program OGO Sense practices in the field of IT support and maintenance with focus on Client training and communication, Joomla CMS website managment and CentOS administration.

09.2014 - 11.2014 Intern *E-Info*

In this practice, I worked with MSSQL databases, I was introduced to the basics of Delphi programming language and creating a form for entering and collecting data from the database via the Delphi. Also, I was introduced to the design of the database via MSSQL, installing Windows and Linux OS systems and MSSQL Server installation. I also worked in Embarcadero Framework.

10.2013 - 11.2013 Census Instructor

Census BIH/RS

Managing and leading census team; Educating census taker; Census field work.

Plastic d.o.o

Selling a variety of plastic goods and items; Conducted client assessments; Supply and delivery of plastic goods.

Education-

10.2016 – 12.2016

JavaScript Course

ICBL

Basic of JavaScript programming language

12.2015 – 05.2015

PHP & MySQL Course

ICBL

PHP and web development

07.2015 – 08.2015

WordPress Course

Installing WordPress and creating WP websites.

01.2015 - 05.2015 Beginner JAVA Course

ICBL

ICBL

Basic of JAVA programming language

09.2014 - 11.2014 Team Work Course

ICBL

Course about working in the teams and large groups.

05.2014 – 03.2015 Beginner, Advance and OOP PHP & MySQL Course

InfoARS Banja Luka

Learning about PHP and web development

10.2003 - 07.2008 Graduated demographer

Faculty of Science in Banja Luka

Demography and Population studies.

Skills				
Languages				
	PHP, Laravel, Blade, Twig, Slim, Rest API			
	HTML, CSS, Pug, SASS			
	JavaScript, ES6, AJAX, VueJS, NodeJS, Gulp, Webpack, Parcel, Browser-Sync, JSON, PWA			
	Git, GitHub, JIRA, Trello, Google Map API			
Databases				
	MySQL, Firebase, MongoDB			
Hardware/Systems	PC/Server, Windows Server OS, Linux Server OS			

— Portfolio ————

Projects:

https://goranradmanovic.github.io

https://stealio.com/

https://www.aleacontrol.com

https://demo.aleacontrol.net/aleabet/#/

https://demo.aleacontrol.net/aleabetlist/#/

http://www.goranradmanovic.byethost13.com/

http://www.bplace.byethost13.com/

http://slim-cms.byethost13.com/public/

https://www.oomovers.com/

https://fbddev.foodbusiness.services/

https://table-app-63709.web.app/

https://nostalgic-engelbart-68f895.netlify.com/

Н		h	h	les
	ıU	U	U	につ